Hell wants him. Heaven won't take him. Earth needs him.
Constantine is a fantasy, action, horror film directed by Francis Lawrence.
John Constantine has literally been to Hell and back.
When he teams up with a policewoman to solve the mysterious suicide of her twin sister, their investigation takes them
through the world of demons and angels that exists beneath the landscape of contemporary Los Angeles.
John Constantine, played by Keanu Reeves.
Angela Dodson / Isabel Dodson, played by Rachel Weisz.
Chas Kramer, played by Shia LaBeouf.
Midnite, played by Djimon Hounsou.
Beeman, played by Max Baker.
Father Hennessy, played by Pruitt Taylor Vince.
Constantine ( KON-stən-TEEN) is a 2005 American supernatural superhero film directed
by Francis Lawrence, and written by Kevin Brodbin and Frank Cappello.
It is loosely based on the Hellblazer comic book series.
The film stars Keanu Reeves as John Constantine, a cynical exorcist with the ability to perceive and
communicate with half-angels and half-demons in their true forms and to travel between Earth and Hell.
The cast also features Rachel Weisz, Shia LaBeouf, Tilda Swinton, Pruitt
Taylor Vince, Djimon Hounsou, Gavin Rossdale and Peter Stormare.
Constantine was released theatrically in the United States on February 18, 2005, to mixed
reviews, and grossed $231 million on a production budget between $70–100 million.
Since its release, it has garnered a cult following.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of self sacrifice, angel,
christianity, confession, superhero.
The tone is dark.